I walked into the gym the other day and wanted to do my workout wearing this
gray catsuit and when I started with my first set the gym staff approached me
and said this is inappropriate I'm not allowed to wear this and they kicked me
out of the gym but is the story real?
No, no way it never happened. It's a total fabrication.
Thanks Jonathan. But now for this video I am really going to show you the catsuit I
talked about and also another catsuit by Bonafide and a third catsuit so let's go
so why did I tell you this story because this is actually workout attire and
made for sports it's a sportswear from a company that has really cool design
and Bonafide I love their stuff and yeah I honestly did not wear it to the gym yet but I've seen
pictures of people doing that and apparently it's a thing in other countries in Germany no one does
that I'm going to add a belt to this one to just give it a bit more of a fashion vibe because I
I love wearing this out for dinner and meeting friends and I discovered that this belt is
a great addition.
For the features we have this middle part which is two layered so it gives a bit more
of a corset feeling and tightens the waist area.
There is this penny cut here in the front which also is in the back.
And these parts here, they push the booty really up because of the difference in fabric. And we also have the bustier part here which makes the boobs look bigger. Also I think these lines here, they make a really nice shape to the hips. So a lot of features.
and also if I open this more you can see that there is this signature
yeah band here which says the name of the company I know that a lot of you don't like this and I
say it's too graphic and too like in your face but I actually love it I think it's a cool design
feature oh and also I'm going to close this for a second if you can see the zipper here
It's basically butt shape.
All in all this is really comfy and yes I can move with it and do things and I could basically work out in it.
Yes it's designed for that. It's stretchy enough, the fabric feels like it's breathable and yeah basically for workout.
But the next one I'm going to show you is more of a daily catsuit, not for workouts but I think it's also a nice one.
Okay, second one. This is basically a wet look, four-letter fabric. It's really, really thin, but also stretchy. And the cut is simpler than with the first catsuit. You have only this line here, also in the back. Otherwise, it's really smooth.
this is no active wear fabric so not for the gym but more for daily wear if you want to wear this
daily and um yeah I think it's also kind of stretchy so I can move around a lot in this one
too but I would like sweat a lot more working out in this one
We have the signature branding here again and also the zipper shape like a butt.
And of course I can close this too.
Now it looks really like a superhero in costume.
Like I am flying on a mission now.
Because it looks really sleek and aerodynamic somehow.
Since it fits really good.
By the way, I'm wearing size small in everything from Bonafide and I could squeeze into extra small, I tried that.
But small is more relaxed when it comes to the fit and also a bit longer, so it fits me better.
And for the last one I have another activewear catsuit, but this time with short arms and different fabric again, so I'll get changed.
As I said, short arms this time but we have this intricate design here again with the
lines down the legs and giving this booty push here since these push the butt a bit
up.
And also what I love with this here is the mesh fabric.
I think it's a great look this.
You can see the skin through the mesh and it gives a nice contrast.
that we have this different kind of fabrics here, more shiny one and a matte one.
So I love their designs and these products and by the way I do have a
discount code you can get 30% off if you use my code you will find it down in the
description text. Anyway Bonapido does not only have catsuits but they have
bodysuits as well for example like this one and I also got another one can show
you some pictures here so yeah you should definitely check out their shop and see for
yourself they launched some oversized t-shirts which I think are really nice too so happy
shopping and I will see you in the next video thanks for tuning in leave a thumbs up and a
comment which one was your favorite also you can check out my patreon for more additional content
on my videos and I will see you in the next one. Have a nice day. Bye!